<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Sophia Roessler Photography</title>
    <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Sophia Roessler Photography</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:10:01 -0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:54924/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Macro Photography</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/macro/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:10:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/macro/</guid>
      <description>Macro Photography allows for a new glimpse at the world and uncovers the details that make each individual and piece of life unique. I enjoy shooting macro as a way to explore our everyday life from a new perspective. Featured below are a few of my favorite shots.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Portraits</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/portraits/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:10:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/portraits/</guid>
      <description>Portraits are one of the fundamentals of photography. Everyone needs a good portrait, whether it&amp;rsquo;s for work, school, or a portfolio. Below are a selection of photos I have taken for scholarship students, artists, creative portraits, and self-portraits.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Seattle Aquarium 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/seattle-aquarium-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 12:10:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/seattle-aquarium-2023/</guid>
      <description>The Seattle Aquarium is filled with many of the beautiful creatures that share our local waters. Not only were they stunning to appreciate in person, but they also made fantastic models. Below are several of my favorites (shoutout to the Spotted Lagoon Jellyfish and the Puffins, they clearly had gone to modeling school).</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>2024 AP Art Portfolio</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/ap-portfolio/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:57:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/ap-portfolio/</guid>
      <description>What is identity? Can art reveal how people develop their unique personalities &amp;amp; represent what the search for self looks like? My visuals dismantle some of the physical factors that have influenced my identity, such as fashion, culture &amp;amp; media, to find meaning in their abstract forms, and depict the search for self in a representational way. My photos serve as a reminder of the strife of identity development. This strife is caused by the perceived presence of imperfection, but, what is an imperfection?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Toronto 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/toronto-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jun 2024 11:57:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/toronto-2023/</guid>
      <description>One of my favorite things to do is use my camera as a way to unpack the personality of a space, or person. During the summer of 2023, I had the chance to visit Toronto and tour the various urban and natural environments that coexist within the city. I noticed that as soon as one stepped outside of the bustling city, an immediate tranquil and natural mood took over. This juxtaposition of energies is something I really tried to capture within this project.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Night of the Arts Posters</title>
      <link>http://localhost:54924/projects/nota/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2024 12:33:01 -0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:54924/projects/nota/</guid>
      <description>The Night of the Arts is an impressive annual art show organized by a handful of high school students and art teachers to showcase the exceptional talents of our artistic and musical students. I had the opportunity to contribute to this event by creating the posters for the talent show. The posters we created became an integral part of promoting the event and capturing the essence of the talent show.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
